Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Marketing, 1975-1999; VIII.
  - Street Fair files, 1994-1999; 5.
    - Street Fair 1995 activities (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1995 all copies (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1995 artist contract (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - Street Fair 1995 artist performing and scheduling (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1995 backup (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1995 bills (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1995 budget, April 1995 (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Street Fair 1995 budget meeting notes, 1994-1995 (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - Street Fair 1995 city permits (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - Street Fair 1995 entertainment (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1995 equipment (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1995 final itinerary (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1995 food (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1995 food vendors (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Street Fair 1995 Fulton theater opening (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1995 general notes to itinerary (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1995 maps (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1995 marketing (Box 274, Folder 9-10)
    - Street Fair 1995 master file, August 1995 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1995 meeting minutes (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1995 non-artists participants (Box 275, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1995 parks department materials (Box 275, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1995 post mortem (Box 275, Folder 5)
    - Street Fair 1995 Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra (Box 275, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1995 Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra proposal, 1994-1995 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1995 rentals and other equipment (Box 275, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1995 street animation (Box 275, Folder 9)
    - Street Fair 1995 street decorations, May 1995 (Box 275, Folder 10)
    - Street Fair 1995 technical needs (Box 275, Folder 11)
    - Street Fair 1995 tents (Box 275, Folder 12)
    - Street Fair 1995 volunteers (Box 275, Folder 13)
    - Street Fair 1996 (Box 275, Folder 14-15)
    - Street Fair 1996 animation (Box 275, Folder 16)
    - Street Fair 1996 animation and non-stage performances (Box 275, Folder 17)
    - Street Fair 1996 budget, 1995-1996 (Box 275, Folder 18)
    - Street Fair 1996 Chase Edmonson (Box 275, Folder 19)
    - Street Fair 1996 Chujko Bros Inc (Box 275, Folder 20)
    - Street Fair 1996 contact list, July 1996 (Box 275, Folder 21)
    - Street Fair 1996 corporate development performance, 1996-1997 (Box 275, Folder 22)
    - Street Fair 1996 expense confirmation (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1996 expenses (Box 276, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1996 food (Box 276, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1996 itinerary (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1996 letter to Pittsburgh Broadway Series subscribers, 1996-1998 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Street Fair 1996 letters and press release (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1996 letters to district businesses, 1995-1996 (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1996 logo (Box 276, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1996 maps (Box 276, Folder 9)
    - Street Fair 1996 marketing (Box 276, Folder 10-11)
    - Street Fair 1996 meeting notes and agendas, 1995-1996 (Box 276, Folder 12)
    - Street Fair 1996 meetings (Box 276, Folder 13)
    - Street Fair 1996 memos and correspondence (Box 276, Folder 14)
    - Street Fair 1996 performers, August 1996 (Box 276, Folder 15)
    - Street Fair 1996 performing artists, July 1996 (Box 276, Folder 16)
    - Street Fair 1996 permits (Box 276, Folder 17)
    - Street Fair 1996 permits and licenses (Box 276, Folder 18)
    - Street Fair 1996 photographs, September 1996 (Box 277, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1996 police and security (Box 277, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1996 post-mortem, September 1996 (Box 277, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1996 production, August 1996 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1996 real estate reception, August 1996 (Box 277, Folder 5)
    - Street Fair 1996 schedule, August 1996 (Box 277, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1996 Showmobile (Box 277, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1996 stages, August 1996 (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1996 Taylor Rentals (Box 277, Folder 9)
    - Street Fair 1996 technical needs and budget, September 1996 (Box 277, Folder 10)
    - Street Fair 1996 tents (Box 277, Folder 11)
    - Street Fair 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 277, Folder 12-13)
    - Street Fair 1997 agenda, 1996-1997 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - Street Fair 1997 Blue Cross, July 1997 (Box 277, Folder 15)
    - Street Fair 1997 budget and labor, 1996-1997 (Box 277, Folder 16)
    - Street Fair 1997 Chase Edmonson, July 1997 (Box 277, Folder 17)
    - Street Fair 1997 Chujko Bros. Inc (Box 277, Folder 18)
    - Street Fair 1997 contracts (Box 277, Folder 19)
    - Street Fair 1997 expenses (Box 277, Folder 20)
    - Street Fair 1997 folk festival (Box 277, Folder 21)
    - Street Fair 1997 Heinz Hall event, August 1997 (Box 277, Folder 22)
    - Street Fair 1997 insurance, July 1997 (Box 277, Folder 23)
    - Street Fair 1997 insertion orders (Box 277, Folder 24)
    - Street Fair 1997 itinerary, 1996-1997 (Box 277, Folder 25)
    - Street Fair 1997 Kurt Wenner (Box 277, Folder 26)
    - Street Fair 1997 maps (Box 277, Folder 27)
    - Street Fair 1997 marketing, 1996-1997 (Box 277, Folder 28)
    - Street Fair 1997 meetings (Box 277, Folder 29)
    - Street Fair 1997 meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1997 parking, June 1997 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1997 participating arts groups, 1996-1997 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1997 permits (Box 278, Folder 4-5)
    - Street Fair 1997 Port O' Johns, August 1997 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Street Fair 1997 post mortem, September 1997 (Box 278, Folder 7)
    - Street Fair 1997 press, August 1997 (Box 278, Folder 8)
    - Street Fair 1997 programming (Box 278, Folder 9)
    - Street Fair 1997 projected expenses (Box 278, Folder 10)
    - Street Fair 1997 proposed passport (Box 278, Folder 11)
    - Street Fair 1997 restaurant letters, 1996-1997 (Box 278, Folder 12)
    - Street Fair 1997 security (Box 278, Folder 13)
    - Street Fair 1997 signs, September 1997 (Box 278, Folder 14)
    - Street Fair 1998 (Box 278, Folder 15-16)
    - Street Fair 1998 blue cross, 1997-1998 (Box 278, Folder 17)
    - Street Fair 1998 expenses (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Street Fair 1998 itinerary (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - Street Fair 1998 press (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Street Fair 1999 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Street Fair 1999 Chase Edmonson (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - Voices of a New Millennium files, 1996-1999; 6.
    This program series featured a variety of types of performances. From musical concerts, lectures, monologists, etc. The shows usually played at the Byham Theater. The files are arranged chronologically by season and then alphabetically by subject.
    - Voices of a New Millennium, 1996-1998 (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 96, 1996 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 96, October 1996 (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 97, 1997 (Box 280, Folder 4-5)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 97 expenses, 1997 (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 97 newspaper clippings and press releases, 1997 (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 97, 1997 (Box 280, Folder 8-9)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 97, 1997 (Box 281, Folder 1-2)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 97 advertising plan, October 1997 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 97 expenses, 1997 (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 97 program insertions, 1997 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 98, 1997-1998 (Box 281, Folder 6-7)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 98 advertising, 1998 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 98 brochure, 1998 (Box 281, Folder 9)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 98 program insertions, March 1998 (Box 281, Folder 10)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 98, 1998 (Box 281, Folder 11)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 98 Bob, 1998 (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Fall 98 program, 1998 (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 99, 1998-1999 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 99, 1999 (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Voices of a New Millennium Spring 99 WYEP logos (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - Production marketing files, 1989-1999; 7.
    Contained in this series are the production marketing files for several of the Cultural Trusts programs. Most of the productions are from the Pittsburgh Broadway Series, but there also productions from the Live on Stage series and other Trust presentations. Each production may have files on each of the following topics – advertising, expenses, gross potential, press clippings press packet, promotions, settlement, tear sheets (newspaper advertising clippings), and ticket sales. In most cases the advertising files contain information on newsprint, television, and radio. Productions that have a greater amount of files attributed to them are Phantom of the Opera (opened 7/24/1993), Miss Saigon (opened 8/06/1997), Chicago (opened 1/12/1998), Rent (opened 5/25/1998), and Showboat (opened 8/21/1998). The productions are arranged chronologically according to it's opening.
    - Steve Lawrence and Eddie Gorme, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Jackie Mason, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Gypsy box office statements, September 1989 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Gypsy expenses, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Gypsy sales reports, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Starlight Express ticket sales, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Red Army Chorus, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - Harlem Boys Choir, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - Nutcracker pre-settlement, 1989 (Box 283, Folder 10)
    - Les Miserables, 1989-1990 (Box 283, Folder 11)
    - Les Miserables costumes, 1990 (Box 283, Folder 12)
    - Cat on a Hot Tin Roof ticket sales, 1990 (Box 283, Folder 13)
    - Shirley MacLaine Out There Tonight, 1990 (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Africa Oye settlement, 1990 (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - M Butterfly, 1990 (Box 284, Folder 3-4)
    - Late Great Ladies of Blues and Jazz, 1991 (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Grand Hotel, 1991 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Grand Hotel daily ticket counts, 1991 (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - the Clancy Brothers marketing and advertising, 1991 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - Jerome Robbins Broadway marketing settlement, 1991 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - Meet Me in St. Louis marketing settlement, 1991 (Box 285, Folder 2-3)
    - Bye Bye Birdie marketing settlement, 1991 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - Buddy Holly ticket sales, 1991 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - A Chorus Line ticket sales, 1991-1992 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Private Lives, 1992 (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Private Lives ticket sales, 1992 (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - Cats, 1991-1992 (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Cats ticket sales, 1991-1992 (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Man of la Mancha, 1991-1992 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Man of la Mancha invoices, 1992 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Man of la Mancha ticket sales, 1992 (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Dinosaurs, Dinosaurs, Dinosaurs, 1992-1993 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Will Rogers Follies, 1992-1993 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Alvin Ailey, 1993 (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Jesus Christ Superstar, 1993 (Box 286, Folder 9)
    - Phantom of the Opera advertising samples, 1991-1993 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera amortized expenses, 1992-1993 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera amortized expenses advertising, 1991-1993 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera banner, 1993 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Phantom of the Opera benefit performance, 1993 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Phantom of the Opera booking, 1989-1993 (Box 287, Folder 6-8)
    - Phantom of the Opera commission sales, 1993 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera contract, July 1992 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 288, Folder 3-6)
    - Phantom of the Opera correspondence, 1993 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera cumulative reports, 1993 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera event reports, 1993 (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera gross potential, 1993 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Phantom of the Opera group sales, 1992-1993 (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Phantom of the Opera hearing impaired performances, 1993 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Phantom of the Opera load out reconciliation, 1993-1994 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera notes, 1991-1992 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera planning, 1993 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera press conference, 1992 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Phantom of the Opera press conference, 1992-1993 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - Phantom of the Opera press packet and photographs, 1992-1993 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Phantom of the Opera reports, 1993 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - Phantom of the Opera technical affairs, 1992-1993 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera ticketing, 1992-1993 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera ticketing invoices, 1993 (Box 291, Folder 3-4)
    - Diary of Anne Frank, 1993 (Box 291, Folder 5-6)
    - My Fair Lady, 1993 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Aurora's Wedding, 1993 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Crazy for You, 1993 (Box 292, Folder 3-4)
    - Crazy for You tear sheets, 1993 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Nutcracker pre-settlement, 1993 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Annie Get Your Gun, 1993-1994 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Annie Get Your Gun press packet, 1993 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Annie Get Your Gun tear sheets, 1993-1994 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Sisters Rosensweig, 1993-1994 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Sisters Rosensweig tear sheets, 1994 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Five Guys Named Moe, 1993-1994 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - Five Guys Named Moe, 1993-1994 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Five Guys Named Moe tear sheets, 1994 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Ghost Stories, 1993-1994 (Box 294, Folder 3-4)
    - Cats, 1994 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Tom Sawyer, 1994 (Box 294, Folder 6-7)
    - Peking Acrobats, 1993-1994 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Peking Acrobats press packet, 1994 (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - the Who's Tommy, 1993-1994 (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - the Who's Tommy press packet, 1994 (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - the Who's Tommy tear sheets, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - La boheme, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 2-3)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Guys and Dolls press packet, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Guys and Dolls tear sheets, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Evita, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Evita tear sheets, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - an Italian Straw Hat, 1994 (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - an Italian Straw Hat, 1994 (Box 296, Folder 1-2)
    - an Italian Straw Hat children's reviews, September 1994 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - an Italian Straw Hat final marketing settlement, 1994 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - an Italian Straw Hat Kennedy Center, 1993-1994 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - an Italian Straw Hat study guide, 1994 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - an Italian Straw Hat ticket audits, 1994 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Blood Brothers settlement, October 1994 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Rosa: the Rosa Parks Story, 1994 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - Rosa: the Rosa Parks Story children's reviews, October 1994 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Rosa: the Rosa Parks Story Philadanco, 1994 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Rosa: the Rosa Parks Story settlement, 1994 (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - Freedom Bound, 1994-1995 (Box 297, Folder 9-10)
    - Freedom Bound Mad River Theater Works, 1994-1995 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Red Badge of Courage, 1994-1995 (Box 298, Folder 2-3)
    - Red Badge of Courage children's reviews, April 1995 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - Angels in America, 1995 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Children's Festival Chorus, 1995 (Box 298, Folder 6-7)
    - Children's Festival Chorus settlement, 1995 (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - Macbeth, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 1-2)
    - the Boys Choir of Harlem, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 3-4)
    - the Boys Choir of Harlem advertising, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - the Boys Choir of Harlem advertising schedules, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - the Boys Choir of Harlem marketing, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - First Night button sales, 1995 (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Jelly Roll! the Music and the Man, 1995-1996 (Box 299, Folder 9-10)
    - Cats, 1995-1996 (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Pickle Family Circus, 1995-1996 (Box 300, Folder 1-3)
    - Pickle Family Circus advertising, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - Pickle Family Circus advertising art, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - Pickle Family Circus Bayer employee order forms, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - Pickle Family Circus broadcast advertising, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - Pickle Family Circus City Theatre offer, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - Pickle Family Circus Fantastic Sam's employee order forms, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - Pickle Family Circus Fantastic Sam's employee order forms, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Pickle Family Circus Pittsburgh Dance Council offer, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Pickle Family Circus Pittsburgh Public Theater offer, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 12)
    - Pickle Family Circus Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra offer, February 1996 (Box 300, Folder 13)
    - Pickle Family Circus proposed marketing and promotion plan, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 14)
    - David Copperfield, January 1996 (Box 300, Folder 15)
    - Annie, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 16)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, May 1996 (Box 300, Folder 17)
    - Funny Girl, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 18)
    - Funny Girl advertising, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 19)
    - Funny Girl bills, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 20)
    - Funny Girl marketing, September 1996 (Box 300, Folder 21)
    - Funny Girl press, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 22)
    - Funny Girl press kit, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 23)
    - Funny Girl settlement, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 24)
    - Funny Girl ticket sales, 1996 (Box 300, Folder 25)
    - River City Brass Band, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - River City Brass Band press kit, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - Steve Love's New York Express Roller Dance Company, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - Steve Love's New York Express Roller Dance Company press packet and photographs, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Steve Love's New York Express Roller Dance Company receipts, October 1996 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe advertising, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe bills, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe marketing, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 8)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe press, 1996 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe press packet, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe settlement, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Smokey Joe's Cafe ticket sales, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Grease advertising, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - Grease affidavits, 1996-1997 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - Grease bills, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - Grease marketing, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Grease press packet, 1996 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Grease settlement, 1996 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - Grease ticket sales, 1996 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - West Side Story advertising, 1996 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - West Side Story bills, 1996 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - West Side Story marketing, 1996-1997 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - West Side Story press, December 1996 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - West Side Story press packet, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - West Side Story ticket sales, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - Barrymore advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - Barrymore bills, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Barrymore marketing, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Barrymore press, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Barrymore press packet, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - Barrymore settlement, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Barrymore ticket sales, 1996-1997 (Box 304, Folder 10)
    - Uptown String Quartet, 1996-1997 (Box 305, Folder 1-4)
    - Uptown String Quartet settlement, 1996-1997 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - Deathtrap advertising, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - Deathtrap bills, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - Deathtrap marketing, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 8)
    - Deathtrap photographs, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 9)
    - Deathtrap press, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 10)
    - Deathtrap press packet, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 11)
    - Deathtrap settlement, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 12)
    - Deathtrap ticket sales, 1996-1997 (Box 305, Folder 13)
    - David Copperfield, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 1-2)
    - David Copperfield marketing, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - David Copperfield press, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - David Copperfield press packet, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - David Copperfield ticket sales, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 7-8)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird advertising, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 9)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird press packet, 1996-1997 (Box 306, Folder 10)
    - To Kill a Mockingbird receipts, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 11)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying advertising, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 12)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying advertising, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 13)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying marketing, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 14)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying press, 1997 (Box 306, Folder 15)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying press packet, 1996-1997 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying settlement, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - How to Succeed in Business without Really Trying ticket sales, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 3)
    - A Chorus Line advertising, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 4-5)
    - A Chorus Line bills, April 1997 (Box 307, Folder 6)
    - A Chorus Line discount offers, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 7)
    - A Chorus Line expenses, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 8)
    - A Chorus Line marketing, 1996-1997 (Box 307, Folder 9)
    - A Chorus Line newspaper clips, 1997 (Box 307, Folder 10)
    - A Chorus Line press, 1996-1997 (Box 307, Folder 11)
    - A Chorus Line press packet, 1996-1997 (Box 307, Folder 12)
    - A Chorus Line settlement, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 1-2)
    - A Chorus Line ticket sales, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Stomp, 1996-1997 (Box 308, Folder 4-6)
    - Stomp booking advisories, October 1996 (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Stomp insertion orders, May 1997 (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Stomp marketing plan, July 1997 (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Stomp marketing publicity and promotion handbook, 1996-1997 (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Stomp marketing settlement, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Stomp press, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - Stomp promotional materials, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - Stomp receipts, June 1997 (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - Stomp settlement, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - Stomp ticket sales, 1997 (Box 308, Folder 16)
    - Miss Saigon, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Miss Saigon actor's fund benefit, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Miss Saigon ad proposals, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 3-4)
    - Miss Saigon additional advertising, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon advance sales reports, 1997 (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 309, Folder 7-9)
    - Miss Saigon advertising and promotional expenses through August 3, 1997 (Box 310, Folder 1-2)
    - Miss Saigon advertising and promotional expenses through August 3, 1997 (Box 311, Folder 1-4)
    - Miss Saigon advertising week two, 1997 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon advertising week five, 1997 (Box 311, Folder 6)